So now let's talk about AWS CodeArtifact.
So software packages the developer creates depends usually
on each other to be built,
and so there's like an architecture of software packages.
And so it's called also code dependencies.
And so to store and retrieve these dependencies,
it's called artifact management.
And so traditionally,
you need to set up your own artifact management system
maybe on Amazon S3
or using some custom software on EC2 instances,
and that may be complicated.
So AWS came up with CodeArtifact, which is a secure,
scalable and cost-effective artifact management software,
service for software development, sorry.
And so what that means is that now,
instead of setting up your own infrastructure,
you can just use CodeArtifact,
and all the common dependency management tools
that developers use, such as Maven, Gradle, npm,
yarn, twine, pip, and NuGet,
can just talk to CodeArtifact
to store and retrieve these code dependencies.
So your developers now have a place by default
that's secure to store and retrieve these dependencies,
and that means that once you push your code to CodeCommit
and CodeBuild we'll build it, then CodeBuild
can also retrieve the dependencies directly
from CodeArtifact.
So from an exam perspective,
CodeArtifact is going to be very helpful
if your team needs a artifact management system
or a place to store their code dependencies.
So that's it.
I hope you liked it,
and I will see you in the next lecture.